<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Kartoon Cafe</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_home">Kartoon Cafe</string>
    <string name="menu_gallery">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="menu_menu">Menu</string>
    <string name="menu_table_reservation">Table Reservation</string>
    <string name="menu_share">Share</string>
    <string name="menu_account">My Account</string>
    <string name="title_activity_sub_menu">SubMenuActivity</string>
    <string name="price">₹ %1$</string>
    <string name="welcome">"Welcome Back,"
                            " Sahil Sharma" 
    </string>
    <string name="KC_contact">9873661199</string>
    <string name="KC_Email">KartoonCafe2017@gmail.com</string>
    <string name="KC_address">The Fusion House, 246,
        Block C4F, Janakpuri,
        New Delhi, Delhi
        110058</string>
    <string name="about_us">Kartoon Cafe is one of kind cafe who
              Offers A Delicious And Multi-Cuisine To Provide
              A Expert Culinary Experience For Our Customers.
        Our Promoters Have Extensively Experience
        of Around The World And they are expert in
        Refined Understanding Of Food and quality. and on
        behalf of that experience they developed kartoon cafe
        recipes for our Valuable customers.</string>

    <string name="juice1">The freshness of watermelon squeezed in a glass</string>
    <string name="juice2">Apple Cedar Juice</string>
    <string name="juice3">The Indian style Mango Juice</string>
    <string name="juice4">Minty Muddled lime soda</string>
    <string name="juice5">Refreshing mojito drink with watermelon infusion</string>
    <string name="juice6">Ginger ale with all the goodness of added herbs for summer</string>
    <string name="juice7">Perfect summer drink featuring Curacao, lemons and mint</string>
    <string name="juice8">Lemon/Peach</string>
    <string name="juice9">Sweet/Salted</string>
    <string name="juice10">Blend of tomato juice with Worcestershire, Tabasco and dash of lemon and pepper</string>
    <string name="juice11">null</string>
    <string name="shake1">Milk shakes of your choice Vanilla/Strawberry/Chocolate</string>
    <string name="shake2">The sweet Banana shake prepared in Banoffee style</string>
    <string name="shake3">Kid\'s love Oreo cookies and now Oreo shakes topped with donut</string>
    <string name="shake4">Summer special Mango shake with whipped cream on the top 195.00</string>
    <string name="shake5">Meal for the day. Is it?</string>
    <string name="shake6">The taste of cheesecake with strawberry in a shake</string>
    <string name="salad1">Herb Grilled Chicken and Celery salad with choice of dressing Balsamic/Lemon</string>
    <string name="salad2">Super Healthy Quinoa mixed with lettuce and grill veggies tossed in home spiced lemon dressing</string>
    <string name="salad3">Grilled seasonal fruits tossed in lemon dressing topped feta cheese balls and roasted wall nuts</string>
    <string name="salad4">Hearty salad of Boiled eggs generously mixed with lettuce and black olives</string>
    <string name="drink1">Choice Of Vanilla/Strawberry/Chocolate/Mocha/Butterscotch</string>
    <string name="drink2">Thick and creamy milkshake infused with peanut butter</string>
    <string name="drink3">Rich and healthy all time favorite delicious banana shake</string>
    <string name="drink4">Indian spiced up buttermilk unbelievably flavorful and refreshing</string>
    <string name="drink5">null</string>
    <string name="crunch1">Oat crusted grilled fish served with mashed potatoes and steam veggies</string>
    <string name="crunch2">A healthy pizza made out of whole wheat crust</string>
    <string name="crunch3">Tangy, Spicy, juicy, tossed in peri-peri sauce, made perfection to order</string>
    <string name="crunch4">Healthier whole wheat pasta in tomato sauce with herb grilled veggies/chicken</string>
    <string name="crunch5">Freshly made to order stone baked Pita with homemade hummus.</string>
    <string name="crunch6">Durum Wheat wrapped veggies and chicken, steamed, soft, flavourful healthy, homemade, served with assortment of dips</string>
    <string name="crunch7">Herbs, grilled and marinated in mustard yoghurt dressing in multigrain bread served with healthy green salad</string>
    <string name="crunch8">Fresh Vegetables &amp; Oats, Savoury pancakes Served with hash Potatoes</string>
    <string name="crunch9">Pieces of Chicken Grilled to Perfection with Dried Herbs, Served With Corns</string>
    <string name="croissants1">Classic French cheese loaded croissant, crispy outside and buttery flaky inside with a filling.</string>
    <string name="croissants2">Cheese Croissant with a filling of vegetarian, chicken or ham combined with our choicest condiments.</string>
    <string name="croissants3">Croissant topped with lots of fresh chocolate</string>
    <string name="breakfast1">Crispy waffles topped with chocolate sauce and roasted nuts served with fresh fruits and Vanilla Ice Cream Scoop</string>
    <string name="breakfast2">Freshly prepared multilayer pan cakes filled with fresh fruits topped with maple syrup served with Vanilla Ice Cream Scoop</string>
    <string name="breakfast3">Choice of egg: Poached/ Sunny side up/ Scrambled, served with toasted bread and hash brown potato</string>
    <string name="breakfast4">Egg white/regular omlette with your choice of veggies /chicken served with toasted bread and hash brown potato.</string>
    <string name="breakfast5">French toast with richness of flavors from cinnamon and vanilla served with maple syrup, fresh fruits and whipped cream.</string>
    <string name="soup1">Slowly roasted tomatoes with garlic finished with sweet basil. Served with 1 pc. Fresh Garlic bread</string>
    <string name="soup2">Wild mushroom cooked with hand full of thyme finished with milk froth.Served with 1 pcs. Fresh Garlic bread</string>
    <string name="soup3">Hearty stock flavored with fresh coriander and lemon.</string>
    <string name="soup4">Chinese style thick mixed vegetable soup topped with crisp fried noodles.</string>
    <string name="soup5">Oriental style peppery chicken, spinach and egg drop soup.</string>
    <string name="soup6">Hearty mix green salad contains mix lettuce, baby spinach tossed fresh lemon dressing</string>
    <string name="soup7">Classical Salad made of crunchy iceberg lettuce tossed in freshly made in house creamy Caesar dressing</string>
    <string name="starters1">Crispy fried rolls filled with flavorful finely sliced veggies served with hot &amp; sweet garlic dip</string>
    <string name="starters2">Freshly made to order stone baked Pita with homemade hummus</string>
    <string name="starters3">Golden fried vegetable/chicken balls tossed in Chinese spices.</string>
    <string name="starters4">All time favorite Chilli chicken with Chef’s special touch.</string>
    <string name="starters5">Hot and juicy finger licking chicken wings/Popcorns with homemade barbeque sauce and masaala Potato Sticks</string>
    <string name="starters6">Stir Fried rice generously mixed with vegetables/egg/chicken</string>
    <string name="starters7">All time kids’ favorite noodles made with all fresh in-house blends</string>
    <string name="starters8">Freshly baked garlic loaf topped with butter or loaded with cheese</string>
    <string name="starters9">Nuggets cooted in herbs and spices, juicy, tender. … Served with french fries and saute seasonal vegetables</string>
    <string name="burger1">Grilled Veggies and cottage cheese patty perfectly pan seared &amp; arranged in fresh baked bun, served with side salad and fries.</string>
    <string name="burger2">Mexican style spicy chicken patty with cheese in fresh baked multigrain bun served with tangy salsa, sour cream and fries.</string>
    <string name="burger3">Rosemary flavored lamb minced cooked to perfection arranged in fresh baked bun, served with side salad and fries.</string>
    <string name="burger4">Cheesy thyme flavored chicken grilled in country style bread served with side salad and fries.</string>
    <string name="burger5">Marinated zucchini, mushrooms, peppers &amp; broccoli put together in focaccia bread for grilling, served with side salad and fries.</string>
    <string name="burger6">Multi-layered sandwich filled with tender grilled paneer/chicken, tomatoes, lettuce, fried egg and cheese slice served with side salad and fries.</string>
    <string name="pizza1">All time favorite cheese loaded pizza.</string>
    <string name="pizza2">Classic combination of mozzarella, tomato and basil.</string>
    <string name="pizza3">Grilled peppers and onion Pizza.</string>
    <string name="pizza4">Fiery smoked chicken sausage combined with black olives and jalapeño.</string>
    <string name="pizza5">Classic Spicy Italian pepperoni pizza.</string>
    <string name="pizza6">Homemade barebeque chicken, so tender and juicy combined with roast garlic and onions.</string>
    <string name="pizza7">null</string>
    <string name="pizza8">Italian folded cheese lovers pizza filled with grilled veggies/chicken, mozzarella and tomato sauce loaded with cheese.</string>
    <string name="pasta1">Chef’s special pasta tossed in freshly made arrabiatta sauce finished with parmesan cheese and fresh sweet basil</string>
    <string name="pasta2">Experience the combination of tomato and cream sauce with hint of garlic finished chopped parsley and parmesan.</string>
    <string name="pasta3">So creamy mushroom sauce pasta with hint of thyme and garlic finished with grated parmesan &amp; fresh black pepper.</string>
    <string name="pasta4">Very special meat sauce spaghetti pasta tossed in garlic and topped with meat balls and grated parmesan.</string>
    <string name="pasta5">Homemade multilayer baked pasta filled with grilled veggies/ mince chicken/lamb mince topped with tomato sauce, béchamel and loads of cheese.</string>
    <string name="pasta6">Risotto provide quick energy conerted into glucose. Chicken and seafood varieties have their own health benefits which are umatched in any other category</string>
    <string name="mexico1">Tortilla filled with veggies/chicken topped with tomato sauce, cheese and baked served with beans, rice, sour cream and salsa</string>
    <string name="mexico2">Tortilla filled with veggies/chicken and cheese served with salsa and sour cream.</string>
    <string name="mexico3">Crispy Tortilla Shells filled with Veggies/Chicken and Mexican salad served with sour cream and salsa</string>
    <string name="mexico4">Crispy nacho chips topped with spicy beans and cheese and sour cream and salsa.</string>
    <string name="dimsums1">Finely chopped aromatic veggies dimsums flavored with mince ginger &amp; garlic, served with assortment of dips.</string>
    <string name="dimsums2">Minced mushroom dimsums flavored with Thai chilli and lemongrass, served with assortment of dips.</string>
    <string name="dimsums3">American twist dimsums filled with creamy corn and spinach, served with assortment of dips</string>
    <string name="dimsums4">Original Asian style Chicken dimsums with blend of homemade spices and herbs, served with assortment of dips.</string>
    <string name="dimsums5">For the meat lovers, minced lamb meat dimsums flavored with rosemary and garlic, served with assortment of dips</string>
    <string name="parade1">Dum Cooked aromatic basmati rice with tender chicken/vegetables, served with burani raita</string>
    <string name="parade2">Sizzle your palate with our thrilling sizzlers, Continental Style/Indian Style/Oriental Style</string>
    <string name="parade3">Japanese delicacy prepared with flavored sticky rice rolled with seafood/vegetables</string>
    <string name="parade4">Freshly picked sole fish grilled and served with creamy mashed potatoes, grill veggies and lemon butter sauce</string>
    <string name="parade5">Traditional Chinese stir-fried dish made with chicken, peanuts, vegetables, and peppers.</string>
    <string name="parade6">Crumb fried fresh sole fish fillets served with hot French fries and homemade tartar sauce.</string>
    <string name="parade7">Stuffed grilled chicken breast glazed with in house rich brown sauce served with mashed potatoes and grill veggies</string>
    <string name="parade8">Oriental style pan fried prawns tossed in homemade sweet and sour sauce.</string>
    <string name="parade9">Oriental Flavored rice or noodles Served with hot &amp; juicy Chicken/Paneer</string>
    <string name="platter1">One Veg Starter, Dal, Paneer Makhani, Indian bread and Steam Rice with accompaniments: green salad and mint chutney</string>
    <string name="platter2">One Non. Veg Starter, Dal, Butter Chicken/Mutton Rogan Josh, Indian bread and Steam Rice with accompaniments: green salad and mint chutney</string>
    <string name="platter3">Dal, Paneer Makhani/Butter Chicken/Mutton Rogan Josh, Indian Bread or Steam Rice with accompaniments: green salad and mint chutney.</string>
    <string name="platter4">Assortments of Non-veg kebabs: Chicken Afghani, Fish Tikka and Galauti Kebab</string>
    <string name="platter5">Assortments of veg kebabs: hara bhara kebab, paneer tikka and onion flower blossom</string>
    <string name="chinese1">One Soup, Veg. Starter, Stir Vegetables and Noodles or fried rice with accompaniments: kimchi salad and homemade Chinese Dips</string>
    <string name="chinese2">One Soup, Non Veg Starter, Sichuan Style Stir Fried Chicken and Noodles or fried rice with accompaniments: kimchi salad and homemade Chinese Dips</string>
    <string name="chinese3">Stir Vegetables/ Sichuan Style Stir Fried Chicken and Noodles or fried rice with accompaniments: kimchi salad and homemade Chinese Dips.</string>
    <string name="arabic1">Greek Salad, French Fries and Falafel Gyro with accompaniments: Hummus and Tzatziki</string>
    <string name="arabic2">Greek Salad, French Fries and Chicken/Lamb Gyro with accompaniments: Hummus and Tzatziki</string>
    <string name="arabic3">Fries and Falafel/Chicken/Lamb Gyro with accompaniments: Hummus and Tzatziki</string>
    <string name="dessert1">Original Classic baked delicious cheesecake.</string>
    <string name="dessert2">Delightful striped chocolate and vanilla cheesecake.</string>
    <string name="dessert3">Delicious creamy and smooth cheese cake topped with mango mousse.</string>
    <string name="dessert4">Original Classic baked delicious cheesecake topped with loads of blue berries.</string>
    <string name="dessert5">Ultimate Fudgy Dark Chocolate Brownie served with scoop of Vanilla Ice Cream topped with hot chocolate sauce.</string>
    <string name="dessert6">Rich Creamy baked yoghurt flavored with saffron.</string>
    <string name="dessert7">Molted chaco lava cake served with a scoop of vanilla ice cream</string>
    <string name="dessert8">Honey &amp; Sesame coated crisp apple served with ice cream</string>
    <string name="dessert9">A rich cold dessert layered with Gulab Jamun and rosy cream</string>
    <string name="dessert10">Classic English dessert made from bananas, cream and caramel combined on a buttery biscuit base</string>
    <string name="dessert11">Classic baked cheese cake flavored with strawberry</string>
    <string name="dessert12">Original Classic baked delicious cheesecake.</string>
    <string name="dessert13">null</string>
    <string name="dessert14">Tangy lemon flavor creamy texture souffle</string>
    <string name="dessert15">Traditional Phirni served in western style</string>
    <string name="dessert16">Tiramisu Cheese Cake</string>
    <string name="dessert17">Nutella Cheese Cake</string>
    <string name="title_activity_order_ahead_sub_menu">OrderAheadSubMenu</string>


</resources>
